let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How many toes are on each foot?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
        "11",
        "14",
        "5",
        "1"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 2,
    question: "Are toes ediable?",
    answer: "No",
    options: [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "On occasion",
        "They are suckable"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 3,
    question: "How many toes are on both feet?",
    answer: "10",
    options: [
        "69",
        "10",
        "5",
        "None"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 4,
    question: "How many joints are in the foot",
    answer: "33",
    options: [
        "45",
        "23",
        "33",
        "15"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 5,
    question: "How much percentage of your bones are in your feet?",
    answer: "25%",
    options: [
        "13%",
        "50%",
        "25%",
        "26%"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "How long does it take for you to grow a brand new toe-nail?",
    answer: "5-6 months",
    options: [
        "5-6 months",
        "3-4 months",
        "3-4 weeks",
        "1 year"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "Do animales has toes?",
    answer: "yes",
    options: [
        "Yes",
        "No",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "Why do feet stink?",
    answer: "Bacteria",
    options: [
        "Left over mayo left in shoes",
        "Bacteria",
        "No feet",
        "Lack of hygiene"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the record for longest big toe?",
    answer: "5inches",
    options: [
        "12inches",
        "3inches",
        "5inches",
        "10 inches"
    ]
},
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is a commen foot condition?",
    answer: "Bunions",
    options: [
        "Onions",
        "Bunions",
        "Menopause",
        "Satellite Tv"
    ]
},



]